Senna, what's this about?
Kobito's Happy Birthday party!
I'm heading into town on Sunday to shop for presents.
Do you think you can make it?
This coming Sunday?
Yeah, I think I'm free.
Sounds good.
Let's meet up around 1 o'clock at the train station.
See you there.
You get me.
Oh!
You ready for some fun?
Tie Rika to a telephone pole and she'll take whatever you give her.
Rika likes to be on top, but she can't resist a forceful man,
the kind that goes in on the first date.
Please call back. Rika's ready and waiting.
Leave me alone.
Read it vertically.
Vertically, huh?
Rika wants you to take her on a date, please.
No can do.
Pretty please?
Rika needs your help in picking a present for Kobito.
Then why didn't you tell me that the first time?
You get me.
For the esteemed Mr. Kodaka Hasegawa.
Dear Mr. Kodaka Hasegawa,
I hope this pleasant fall season has brought you great wealth and prosperity,
particularly in the forging of new friendships.
Please forgive me for the suddenness of this letter.
I know its arrival is unexpected.
I'm terribly sorry to trouble you when you are surely very busy,
but I take pin in hand now because there is something of utmost importance that I must ask you.
There is no other companion I may consult.
I know you are a busy man,
so I shall be so bold as to come straight to the point.
Your sister's birthday is fast approaching.
What should I give to your honored sibling?
With my best wishes for your health and...
I don't have time for a novel.
You get me.
Need your help getting a present for Kobito.
No big deal if you're busy or whatever.
I know how forgetful I'm like you are, but whatever.
Tomorrow would work best, but whatever.
It's not like you absolutely have to be there,
so don't worry if you're like busy or whatever.
And it's super long.
It's not like I can't pick out one little present of my own or whatever.
What's with all the whatevers?
Anyway, I guess I'll see you there.
Oh well.
Hey, what's up?
The next train is now approaching platform 3.
Looks like everyone's here.
Cool.
Guess we better get to it.
Complete stops.
Grab a seat, Yozara. There's one right here.
Shut up. Don't tell me what to do.
What's the rest of the club doing here?
Oh, my bad.
Yeah, I guess I didn't tell you.
Everyone wanted to buy Kobito a present,
so I figured we might as well hit up the mall together.
Still, this probably wasn't the best way for you to go about it.
I mean, it's not a secret that you're pretty dense,
but this is beyond stupidity.
Did I do something wrong?
Never mind, idiot.
Rika had a feeling Kodika was going to let her down again,
but even though you know it's coming, it still sucks.
I, too, feel your pain. I think we all do.
All her studies couldn't have prepared Rika for such a man.
Someone so, so ridiculously oblivious to everything.
Okay.
Oh, but it's really not a big deal.
One day you'll feel Rika's presence emotionally and physically.
I don't think I will.
By the way, why are you wearing your lab coat today?
Why? Is there a problem with it?
You've been obsessed with your hair lately,
but you don't care about your clothes.
It's kind of a strange combination.
Like today, how you're wearing the same clothes,
but also randomly got highlights.
Um, Rika didn't think you would notice.
Aren't you just full of surprises?
But to be honest, Rika has never thought
that worrying about her clothes would make a difference.
There's no incentive considering you don't even pay attention to her
when she's stripping.
Not gonna lie.
I wouldn't mind if she ditched the lab coat
and wore something more revealing.
I take it I somehow said all of that out loud again?
Yeah, you did.
Let's go in the back and make babies.
Oh, yeah.
I've got a question, Senna.
What is it?
Rika wanted to buy some new clothes while we're shopping.
Are there any nice stores you'd recommend?
You want my shopping advice, really?
Rika would love to learn from the master.
You're such a stylish and sexy gal.
Actually, I honestly don't go shopping that often,
and when I do, it's at the fancy name brand places near my house,
so I don't know what to tell you.
The only places close to your house are a few mountains and rice fields.
Is that true, Senna?
No, Miss Senna is fibbing.
You're right. I'm sorry I lied to you.
Stella's the one who picks out all of my clothes.
She styles my hair and puts on my makeup, too.
What was that for?
It's not like you know any better.
Femininity level of only five.
How pitiful.
Hey, neat, a scouter.
While we're at it, where do you buy your clothes, Yozara?
I get all my stuff online.
If I see a model with a decent-looking outfit in a fashion magazine
or on a website, I'll buy the whole thing.
Rika's jealous.
It's awesome that you can look good wearing outfits straight out of a fashion bag.
And today you look especially cute.
This is cute?
Shut up.
Uh-uh.
It's very feminine and such an adorable sort of sexy.
Feminine?
Adorable?
Sexy?
Ah, crap.
Take it back!
This was in the how to look boyish section.
There's no way this can be sexy.
Girl, are you for real?
Yozara, listen to me.
When women rock the boyish look, it doesn't mean they're dressing like a man would.
In fact, it's usually the other way around.
It's a way to draw out your feminine charms by being more androgynous.
Think shorts instead of skirts and knits instead of wolf-ins.
Seriously?
You'd have to be blind not to notice this stuff.
How often do you see dudes strutting around in hot pants and showing off their belly buttons?
But you're the only guy whose wardrobe I ever even noticed.
Huh?
Oh, just forget it!
I'm gonna do some other shopping after I get her gift.
Kodaka, you can't come along.
That's cool.
Are you gonna be okay by yourself?
Rika will keep her company.
Hmm.
Yeah, all right.
Yukimura, do you mind tagging along with Yozara and Rika and keeping them in line?
We wouldn't want them to freak out in the middle of a public place.
Do you know what I mean?
Yes, sir.
I've got it under control.
I'll see you later.
Best of luck shopping for Kobito.
Thanks.
Yeah, you too.
Well then, that's that.
Why don't the two of us start looking around?
Hey, Kodaka, what's something I could buy for Kobito that'd make her like me more?
I know she's into Full Metal Necromancer.
Yeah, but she's pretty much got all the merchandise she could want already.
Oh, and please, don't get her any expensive stuff.
Hmm.
You're a more considerate big brother than I thought.
What would you recommend, then?
I'm almost out of ideas.
How about something you'd like?
I totally want Kobito!
You can't have her.
Hey, over here.
I just thought of a gift I know for sure she'd like.
What's that?
Meat.
I mean meat the food, not meat as in you.
Aw, I knew that.
Don't rub it in.
Steak, bacon, wings, anything.
Get her some jerky and she's yours for life.
Maybe so, but a meat snack's kind of a messed up birthday present, don't you think?
Good point.
Jerky?
What am I thinking?
Meh.
Remember that as a last resort for the time being.
I'm sure we'll find other good stuff.
Oh my gosh, they have it!
They have what?
It's so beautiful.
Hmm?
Seriously, since when is the girl supposed to keep the guy company when they go shopping?
Normally it's the other way around.
Sorry.
What the heck's so special about frying pans anyway?
You've got to be kidding me.
Default pans aren't just any old frying pans.
Here, let me try and break it down for you.
Not necessary.
You are the weirdest person I know.
It's almost kind of really sad.
There's nothing wrong with liking high quality cookware.
You've got a lot more issues than just that one, dummy.
Shut up.
What do you think is taking the girls so long?
Girls always take a long time to finish shopping.
At least they're doing gaming games.
You learned that from a video game?
Hey, Kodika, what do you think of the other girls in the neighbor's club?
Like, do you like them?
What do you mean?
Man, why are you so...
Ugh, never mind.
Do you ever even think about dating and having a girlfriend?
I guess I wouldn't say I don't not want to date.
Thanks for clearing that up.
Well, for right now, my main goal is to make some friends.
Think about it.
A boring guy without any friends isn't going to impress many ladies.
Girls will think of him as a loser.
I don't think that's necessarily true.
Hmm?
Oh, man, how are you so...
Ugh, never mind.
Hey, why do you keep saying that?
A random question.
Um, well, what do you think about the fact that Yozara and I used to be friends?
You know, when we were kids.
Hmm.
I was honestly surprised when you first told us, but then I thought things over.
I don't think it's that big a deal.
In fact, it doesn't matter at all.
You mean you don't care?
Well, I mean, it's in the past, right?
The present is what's really important.
Yeah, I guess you're right.
Still, I haven't quite figured out what Yozara's intentions are with you.
With what?
Never mind.
I doubt I'm going to lose to her anyway.
That's all.
Hey, before I forget.
And this is important, so please make sure you remember it.
Don't think of yourself as boring.
Anybody I like can't be that lame.
Do you have any opinions on Rika's new outfit?
This is what the clerk recommended Rika try on for you.
Oh?
Well, it's...
I'd say that whenever you try to look good, you pull it off nicely.
Rika will interpret that messed up comment as a compliment.
Um, Kodaka?
Do you think I look okay?
Yozara bought something else, so she let me have this.
Damn, Yukimura, that's hot.
Uh, I mean, it looks nice on you.
I'm very glad you like it.
Thank you.
Last but not least...
What the hell is that?
What are you wearing?
I'm so confused, woman.
You're a disaster in black cotton.
Oh, be quiet, flapjacks.
I'm not in the greatest of moods right now.
A tracksuit?
I found it marked down at a sports store.
Don't you like it?
Anyway, all these crowds are making me kind of groggy.
I'll just grab something for Kobudo near my place.
See you later.
Huh?
Rika's gonna head home, too.
Thanks for the fun.
Sorry, Senna.
My bags are getting heavy, and I'm tired of lugging them around.
Not you, too!
I shall accompany you, Kodaka.
You have got to be kidding me!
You guys are so the worst shoppers ever!
There, it's perfect, but no surprise there.
Then again, do you think Kobudo will even enjoy having a birthday party that looks this lame?
Cut us some slack.
No one here actually knows what a normal birthday party looks like.
This'll have to work for now.
Along those same lines, what are people supposed to do at a birthday party?
Do you know, Kodaka?
Uh, well, probably eat cake and open presents most of the time, though that doesn't sound
like a lot of fun.
Maybe everyone plays games.
It's a party, after all.
Fat chance that's gonna happen.
The only games we have are your wonky computer games and Meets' pervy dates.
Oh, please.
There's no way she's not coming.
Rika almost has all the bugs figured out.
Yeah, too bad there aren't any board games in here, though.
We'll just stop by the closest toy store and get one.
How about Twister?
You really are a pervert.
If you're right outside the door, then you should just get in here.
Happy birthday, my sweet darling Kobito!
Likewise.
Happy birthday, Miss Kobito.
Poppers!
Enough with the poppers, guys.
Okay, Kobito, take a seat.
It's time for your cake.
Three, two, one, kick off!
Dig in!
Uh-huh.
What do you think?
Isn't it beautiful?
We're so happy!
Wow, Meat.
Your creepiness never ceases to amaze me.
What's your problem?
That cake is incredible and you know it!
It's a nice day for a birthmas.
Happy birthmas for you.
Who was born today?
It was...
Karla's birthday!
Come on, at least get her name in sync.
Happy birthmas to you.
I hate that.
Well, what are you waiting for?
Blow out your candles.
Oh.
Um, okay then.
Happy birth, Cheech!
There you go.
What'd you do that for, Hobag?
Whoops, my finger slipped.
Open white, Kodaka!
They're each a different scent.
It's a talisman.
So you got her meat.
Raw meat.
Don't mock me.
You're bound to eat some too.
Meat giving meat.
How original.
I've got a good idea.
Let's have sukiyaki tonight.
Pretend that I'm right there
spoon-feeding you my meat of love.
No!
Sukiyaki!
Someone's in a good mood.
Ki-ki-ki.
Today's been an awesome day.
Hey, I've got to pick up some ingredients.
Meet you back home in a little bit, okay?
Do your best not to dawdle, my kinfolk.
Oh, wow.
Yo.
I didn't see you.
Why are you here?
Um, that's my house.
Why are you sneaking around?
Oh, I was just hoping I could catch a glimpse
of how it looks inside.
That's all.
Silly, isn't it?
Yes, it is.
Why do you even care how my place looks?
Big Brother's finally home!
And another unexpected visit.
Did you get Kate to bring you over here?
Yup.
If there's anything the old hag is good for,
it's taking me to see you.
What are you still doing here?
Stinking brat.
Weren't you just begging and pleading?
Please take me, sis.
I'll be grateful forever.
So what was that just now?
Care to explain yourself?
Um, I was...
Get lost, poopy old hag!
Honestly, something's wrong with that girl.
Says the creepy chick who's been spying.
Hey, since you two are here already,
do you want to stay over for dinner?
Seriously?
Both of us?
Uh, yeah.
Just perfect.
This wonderful day has now turned into complete crap.
So you must be Big Brother's one and only real little sister, huh?
Who is your big brother?
Oh, that's what Maria calls Kodika.
She always wanted a bigger brother.
So if I'm her sister and he's also older than me,
then he's my big brother too,
which totally makes you and I sisters.
What's wrong?
Crappy stupid head!
You big fat dummy!
How come you have so many little sisters now?
I'm supposed to be the only sister.
Quit making more!
Whoa, calm down.
They just call me Big Brother.
It doesn't mean anything.
Hey, why did Maria want to come over today?
She said she wanted to talk to Kobito.
Coo-coo-coo.
What business does that foolish minion of God have with me,
supreme ruler of darkness and destruction?
Uh, what just happened?
Just pretend you didn't see that.
Hey, come on, Maria.
Hurry up and give Kobito the present you bought for her.
Maria brought a gift?
Ah!
Why'd you have to open your big mouth, poopy old head?
Why are you freaking out about it?
Here.
I decided to be nice and get you a present,
so you better like it.
Birthdays are kind of important,
even for a poopy vampire like you.
Just open it up and say thanks already.
It's for scaring off evil spirits and spooky stuff.
You should use it to drive out the darkness
from your poopy soul and become a good girl.
Hmm.
What a silly little birthday present.
Divine powers don't work on me.
How dare you?
Repent your dumb sins, you evil poopy vampire.
Your stupid key has no effect.
That's too, poopy vampire.
All right, ladies, it's sukiyaki time.
Ah, sukiyaki?
That's that tasty-sounding meaty dish
that the dumb hag's too stupid to make.
Whee!
Hold on, big brother.
Let me help you set the table.
Go on, Kobito.
Tell Maria thank you for the birthday present.
Thank you.
Ah, poop.
What?
Did you just say something to me?
Never mind, dumb bun.
What was that for, pooper?
Juck race?
Dabby-dabby-toilet-head?
Give me back that breast.
Meal and rip it.
You're pooping it.
Thanks for the awesome meal.
I barely got any beef.
There were at least four pounds worth, too.
Those girls have quite the appetite.
Hey, so do you.
All that food is making me tired.
Hey, Kodika, do you mind if we stay the night?
It's okay by me.
Seriously?
Thanks, bro.
There is no way you're only 15.
Fine, I turned 16 a while back.
Here, check this out.
Maria gave it to me on my birthday.
Hey, that's a nice locket.
What's with the bug?
Maria gave me the cicada shell,
and I got a buddy to make it into a totally wicked necklace.
It's the only thing that girl has ever given me.
Your life has been kind of rough, huh?
Hey, I'm a big sister.
It is what it is.
Maria, big brother's letting us stay for the night.
Come on, get up.
You need a bath.
I want one with big brother.
Hurry it up, girl!
I'm excited to be nice and washing to you.
You better be great!
I'll check and see if we have any pajamas that'll fit you.
Let me go!
Help you open up!
Shut up and hold still!
I'm glad Cobito isn't that hard to deal with.
Hey!
Cobito?
You gonna take a picture?
No, I'm sorry!
I'm so sorry!
No wonder you wanted us to stay the night.
I'm sorry about that, Kate.
Fine.
I forgive you.
Huh?
Well, that was quick.
Well, I'm pretty sure you didn't stumble in on purpose.
Of course I didn't!
Jeez!
Exactly!
So it's not worth getting all pissed off at you.
It's cool that you're not making up excuses or trying to defend yourself.
Yeah, when I do something bad, I think it's best to own up to it.
You really are a halfway decent guy.
It totally makes sense why Pegasus likes you as much as he does.
Oh, do you and the president know each other?
Sure.
Me and Pegasus are actually fishing buddies.
We go out IU fishing once or twice a month.
Uh, that's super random.
It's fun.
You ought to come along sometime.
Yeah?
Maybe someday.
Hey, thanks for letting us crash.
Till next time.
Yeah.
See you guys at school.
Ah.
Man.
Sometimes I wish that you really were our bigger brother.
Then again.
To be honest, I wouldn't mind if you were more than just a brother, because that way,
you could walk in on me all the time.
But you do have Senna, so, well, that's out.
Alrighty.
See ya.
It wasn't long before I figured out what Kate was getting at.
It wasn't very long at all.
That was delicious! Let's go home and take a nap.
Hey! Do the preview like a normal person, Hag!
Yeah, whatever, you annoying brat.
Next, my childhood friend is too much of a battleground.
If Big Brother has childhood friends, that means he's all grown up!
I want to have a childhood friend, too!
Don't be dense, you're still in your childhood.
Though in another five years, I bet Kobotel could be your childhood friend.
I don't want no poopy vampire to be my childhood friend!
You and her will be my enemies forever! Take that, poopy Hag!
Fine, fine.
Thank you, Jenga.
Um, it's possible to not understand my heart, just like you said,
I'm so hungry!
Oh no!
I would like that to be so cold!